const yesNo=[!0,!1];let profile={name:null,email:null,age:null,gender:null,inUS:null,diet:null,dietOther:null,nearBelmar:null,commit:null,diagnose:[],diagnoseOther:null,previous:null,exercise:null,exIntense:null,sweat:null,dailyBowel:null,smoke:null,pregnant:null,drink:null,supplements:null,goals:{top:null,mid:null,low:null}};const questions=[{question:"What is your first name?",answer:"name",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:[],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Select your age range",answer:"age",category:"basics",multipleAnsAllow:!1,otherOption:!1,options:["0-13","14-18","19-30","31-45","46-65","65+"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Gender",answer:"gender",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:["Female","Male","Non-binary"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Pregancy",answer:"pregnant",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:["Hope to be pregnant within 1-2 years","Prenatal (currently pregnant)","Postpartum","None of the above / Not Applicable"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Level of commitment",answer:"commit",multipleAnsAllow:!1,otherOption:!1,category:"basics",options:["Skeptical","Interested","Ready to dive in... where do I sign?"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Check off all you've been diagnosed with",answer:"diagnose",multipleAnsAllow:!0,category:"health history",otherOption:!0,options:["Cancer","Lyme","Gut Issues (Celiac)","Neurological (ALS, MS)","Skin Issues (Cystic Acne)","Mystery Illness","Chronic Pain","Hormonal (PCOS, Cycle Issues, Infertility)","Breast Tissue Abnormality","Mental Health (Depression)","None"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Have you previously been to a function medicine practitioner before?",answer:"previous",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Enter your email so we can send you results",answer:"email",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:[],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you reside within the US?",answer:"inUS",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Are you local to Belmar, New Jersey? (within X miles)",answer:"nearBelmar",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"basics",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!0},{question:"Does your diet fall into any of these categories?",answer:"diet",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!0,options:["Vegan","Vegetarian","Paleo","Gluten-Free","Intermittent Fasting","None"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"How many times/week do you exercise?",answer:"exercise",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:["0","1-2","3-5","7+"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"What intensity level is your exercise",answer:"exIntense",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:["Low (walking, yoga)","Moderate (jogging, body weight exercises)","Intense (marathon, HIIT, weight lifting)"],relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you sweat when you exercise? (If you glisten, mark no)",answer:"sweat",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you have a daily bowel movement?",answer:"dailyBowel",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you smoke?",answer:"smoke",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you drink?",answer:"drink",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1},{question:"Do you take any supplements?",answer:"supplements",multipleAnsAllow:!1,category:"lifestyle",otherOption:!1,options:yesNo,relyOnPrior:!1}],quizElement=document.getElementById("quiz");let currentQ=0;function startQuiz(){function postQ(){let i=questions[currentQ];n.innerHTML=null;let e=document.createElement("h1");if(e.innerHTML=i.question,n.appendChild(e),0==i.options.length){let e=document.createElement("input");e.onkeyup=function(e){profile[i.answer]=e.target.value},n.appendChild(e)}else{let l=document.createElement("div");if(l.id="radioInputs",i.options.map(e=>{let t=document.createElement("div");t.classList.add("opWrap");let n=document.createElement("input");0==i.multipleAnsAllow?n.type="radio":n.type="checkbox",n.value=e,n.name="currentQ",n.onclick=function(e){0==i.multipleAnsAllow?profile[i.answer]=e.target.value:e.target.checked?profile[i.answer].push(e.target.value):-1!==(e=profile[i.answer].indexOf(e.target.value))&&profile[i.answer].splice(e,1)};let o=document.createElement("label");o.innerHTML="boolean"==typeof e?e?"Yes":"No":e,t.appendChild(n),t.appendChild(o),l.appendChild(t)}),1==i.otherOption){function checkOtherInput(){document.getElementById("otherBtn").checked&&0<document.getElementById("otherInput").value.length&&(profile[`${i.answer}Other`]=document.getElementById("otherInput").value),console.log(profile)}let e=document.createElement("div");e.classList.add("opWrap");let t=document.createElement("input");0==i.multipleAnsAllow?t.type="radio":t.type="checkbox",t.value="Other",t.name="currentQ",t.id="otherBtn",t.onclick=function(e){checkOtherInput()};let n=document.createElement("label");n.innerHTML="Other:";let o=document.createElement("input");o.id="otherInput",l.onkeyup=function(e){checkOtherInput()},e.appendChild(t),e.appendChild(n),e.appendChild(o),l.appendChild(e)}n.appendChild(l)}let t=document.createElement("button");currentQ<questions.length-1?(t.innerHTML="next",t.onclick=submitQ):(t.innerHTML="next",t.onclick=displayPriorityChart),n.appendChild(t)}function submitQ(){var e=questions[currentQ];null!=profile[e.answer]&&(currentQ++,postQ())}let n=document.createElement("div");n.id="quizBlock",quizElement.appendChild(n),postQ(n)}function displayPriorityChart(){quizElement.innerHTML=null;let e=document.createElement("div");e.id="goalBlock";let t=document.createElement("h1");t.innerHTML="Choose up to 3 HEALTH GOALS and prioritize importance with 1 = most important",e.appendChild(t);let l=document.createElement("div");l.id="goalTable";let n=document.createElement("div");n.id="tableRow";var o=document.createElement("label");n.appendChild(o);for(let t=0;t<3;t++){let e=document.createElement("span");e.innerHTML=t+1,n.appendChild(e)}l.appendChild(n);let i=document.createElement("button");i.disabled=!0,["Digestion","Sleep","Fitness","Stress","Mood","Energy","Brain","Mental Health","Mystery Illness","Overall Health & Prevention"].map(n=>{let o=document.createElement("div");o.id="tableRow";let e=document.createElement("label");e.innerHTML=n,o.appendChild(e);for(let t=0;t<3;t++){let e=document.createElement("input");e.type="radio",e.name=t+1,e.dataset.goal=n,e.onclick=()=>{let e=document.querySelectorAll('[data-goal="'+n+'"]');switch(t){case 0:e[1].checked=!1,e[2].checked=!1,profile.goals.top=n;break;case 1:e[0].checked=!1,e[2].checked=!1,profile.goals.mid=n;break;case 2:e[0].checked=!1,e[1].checked=!1,profile.goals.low=n;break;default:profile.goals.top=n}2<document.querySelectorAll("input:checked").length?i.disabled=!1:i.disabled=!0},o.appendChild(e)}l.appendChild(o)}),e.appendChild(l),i.onclick=displayResults,i.innerHTML="finish",e.appendChild(i),quizElement.appendChild(e)}function displayResults(){document.createElement("div");console.log(`${profile.name}'s Healing Journey`),0==profile.sweat?console.log("Often overlooked, the body’s detoxification process is vital to keep us feeling our best. If you’re unclear on what detoxification is, perfect examples are sweat and sleep. When you sweat youe body is expelling toxins. When you sleep the space between your cells increases, thus increasing the flow of toxins being flushed out. The primary function of your liver, kidneys, and lungs is detoxification, if they’re bogged down, you’re not expelling toxicity out of your body efficiently. "):console.log("If you’re looking to maintain and/or enhance your body’s detoxification pathways, you need to engage in active sweating! Our favorite method is the infrared sauna where you can sweat out your toxins."),profile.supplements&&console.log("At Integrative Wellness Group, we pride ourselves on testing (not guessing). Through IRT (Integrative Response Testing), our team is able to ___ determine what supplements, services, and therapies will benefit you best at every stage of your wellness journey."),console.log("-"),console.log(profile)}startQuiz();